SURYANSH TRIPATHI

My Contact

suryanshtripathi2021@gmail.com

+918787247275

🗣 Hyderabad, Telangana

in www.linkedin.com/in/suryansht ripathi

www.suryanshtripathi.website

Hard Skill

- Microsoft Azure Windows, Linux
- Full Stack Development
- HTML, CSS, Nodejs, Express
- Database Technology (MongoDB, MySQL)
- Programming Languages C, C++

Soft Skill

- Strategic planning
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Problem-solving

H.S.C - 86.80%

Education Background

- 2020-2024 | Amity University
 BTech (Computer Science & Engineering)
 CGPA 8.83
- 2016-2020 | G.N National Public School PCM (Physics, Chemistry, Maths)
 S.S.C - 82.00%

About Me

Graduated with a B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering. Self-motivated and a fast learner, passionate about working with tech companies and keeping up with the latest technology trends. Objectives are to build skills and gain experience through different avenues to become a changemaker.

Work Experience

Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. | Summer Training 29 May 2023 - 30 June 2023

- Build a clone for the official site DISHA used by ONGC for file repo
- Learned about the IBM BPM and the designing part
- Helped portal management team in creating UI designs
- Got the formal overview of the Active Service Directory authentication system

Amity University | In-House Practical Training 30 May 2022 - 10 July 2022

- Build an online food delivery website
- Main objective is to bring the restaurant services online
- Used AJAX to create asynchronous web application
- Used passport-local for the purpose of authentication
- Integrated a contact form to increase the interaction between customers and restaurant

Certifications

Jan 2023 CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks

Sept 2021 Google Cloud
Architecting with Google Compute
Engine Specialization.